Tom Hunter

Games and Software Developer

Summary

Accomplished Software Developer with 4+ years of modern development experience. Practiced problem solver with the ability to analyze problems and design software solutions that are clean, scalable, and well-documented. Flexibility to adapt to new development methodologies, programming conventions, and project environments.

Comfortable with prioritizing and completing tasks while maintaining regular communication with my peers. Self-motivated, respectful, and a true team player. Always seeking new challenges and experiences.

Work Experience

Software Developer @ EB Games Australia (Jul 2021 – Dec 2021)

Worked in an Agile environment to develop and maintain features for many of EB Games' applications, primarily their ecommerce application for <u>ebgames.com.au</u>. Greatly enhanced my development experience and learned a variety of new skills.

Game Designer & Developer @ National Colleges of Australia (Jan 2021 – Jul 2021)

Independently designed, developed, and published multiple small-scale educational learning tools in Unity3D for this startup teacher aides company. Practiced design techniques, client interaction, Unity MLAPI networking, and self-management.

Education

Bachelor of Games and Interactive Environments (Software Technologies) from Queensland University of Technology (QUT), 2017-2020

- Minored in Advanced Software Technologies and Interaction Design.
- Achieved a GPA of 6.33 and two academic performance awards.
- Learnt a variety of software and game development skills.

References

Brendan McGill

EB Games Australia, Software Development Manager brendan.mcgill@ebgames.com

Asher Wildeboer

EB Games Australia, Technical Lead asherw83@gmail.com

Web Portfolio

tomhunter.dev



Skills

- Advanced knowledge of software development using C#
- Game development using Unity3D and Unreal Engine 4
- Web development using HTML, CSS, LESS, JavaScript, Angular, and Razor Pages
- App development using .NET, ASP.NET, NUnit, and Ling
- Familiar with version control, agile, DevOps, iterative development, and the game production pipeline
- Used C++, Python, Java, and Blueprints
- Experience using and integrating AWS and Azure cloud services
- Creating RESTful APIs
- SQL and database integration
- Thread control, algorithms, regex, dependency injection
- Developed apps for PC, MacOS, Linux, and Android
- Studied and applied software design, and UX design
- Modelling/animation using Maya
- Quality assurance

Contact

tomhunter.dev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/tom-w-hunter